[
  {
        "question": "Bus, ring and star topologies are mostly used in the __________.",
        "answers": {
          "a": "LAN",
          "b": "MAN",
          "c": "WAN",
          "d": "Inter-network"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "a"
      },
      {
     
        "question": "In Peer to peer network topology it is not necessary that all PCs should be connected in a network.",
        "answers": {
          "a": "True",
          "b": "False"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "b"
      },
      {

        "question": "Physical or logical arrangement of network is:",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Topology",
          "b": "Routing",
          "c": "Networking",
          "d": "None of the mentioned"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "a"
      },
      {
      
        "question": "Combination of two or more topologies are called:",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Star Topology",
          "b": "Bus Topology",
          "c": "Ring topology",
          "d": "Hybrid Topology"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "d"
      },
      {
    
        "question": "In mesh topology, devices are connected via:",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Multipoint link",
          "b": "Point to point link",
          "c": "No Link",
          "d": "None of the above"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "b"
      },
      {
     
        "question": "A topology that is responsible for describing the geometric arrangement of components that make up the LAN.",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Complex",
          "b": "Physical",
          "c": "Logical",
          "d": "Incremental"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "b"
      },
      {
    
        "question": "Which LAN topology describes the possible connections between pairs of networked end-points that can communicate?",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Complex",
          "b": "Physical",
          "c": "Logical",
          "d": "Inter-network"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "c"
      },
      {
      
        "question": "A _________ is set of devices connected by media links.",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Network",
          "b": "Nodes",
          "c": "Transmission medium",
          "d": "All of the above"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "a"
      },
      {
        
        "question": "Multipoint topology is:",
        "answers": {
          "a": "Bus",
          "b": "Star",
          "c": "Mesh",
          "d": "Ring"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "a"
      },
      {
       
        "question": "Bus topology is also known as line topology or backbone.",
        "answers": {
          "a": "True",
          "b": "False"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "a"
      }
    ]
  


